[
    {
        "front": "ばしょ",
        "back": "場所 \nplace",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひろば",
        "back": "広場 \nplaza",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "けんせつ",
        "back": "建設 \nbuilding construction",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "にもつ",
        "back": "荷物 \nbag",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいいん",
        "back": "退院 \ndischarge",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょかん",
        "back": "旅館 \njapanese style inn",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "びじゅつかん",
        "back": "美術館 \nart gallery / museum",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうどう",
        "back": "講堂 \nlecture hall",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいぎしつ",
        "back": "会議室 \nmeeting room",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "じむしつ",
        "back": "事務室 \noffice room",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうぎょう",
        "back": "工業 \nmanufacturing  industry",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうじ",
        "back": "工事 \nconstruction",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうさく",
        "back": "工作 \nhandicraft",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "としょかん",
        "back": "図書館 \nlibrary",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんごう",
        "back": "信号 \ntraffic signal",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "３ごうしつ",
        "back": "３号室 \nroom number 3",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごうれい",
        "back": "号令 \ncommand",
        "chapter": "N4 K16"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうばん",
        "back": "交番 \npolice box",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "とおる",
        "back": "通る \nto cross",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "かよう",
        "back": "通う \nto commute",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "つうきん",
        "back": "通勤 \ncommuting to work",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "うごく",
        "back": "動く \nto move",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "じょうしゃ",
        "back": "乗車 \nto board (a vehicle)",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうすいりょう",
        "back": "降水量 \nprecipitation amount, rainfall volume",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "はこぶ",
        "back": "運ぶ \nto transport",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "うんちん",
        "back": "運賃 \nfare",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "ころがる",
        "back": "転がる \nto roll, to fall",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "うんてん",
        "back": "運転 \ndriving",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "てんきん",
        "back": "転勤 \njob transfer",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅっぱつ",
        "back": "出発 \ndeparture",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "はつめい",
        "back": "発明 \ninvention",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "はっけん",
        "back": "発見 \ndiscovery",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "きもの",
        "back": "着物 \nkimono",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゃくしん",
        "back": "着信 \nincoming message",
        "chapter": "N4 K17"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅうじ",
        "back": "習字 \ncalligraphy",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぶんがく",
        "back": "文学 \nliterature",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうもん",
        "back": "注文 \norder",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "＊もじ",
        "back": "＊文字 \ncharacter",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "おしえる",
        "back": "教える \nto teach",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうかい",
        "back": "教会 \nchurch",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうかしょ",
        "back": "教科書 \ntextbook",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "べんきょう",
        "back": "勉強 \nstudies",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "ならう",
        "back": "習う \nto learn",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "よしゅう",
        "back": "予習 \npreparation for class",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅうかん",
        "back": "習慣 \ncustom",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "さんこうしょ",
        "back": "参考書 \nreference book",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "かんがえる",
        "back": "考える \nto consider",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "けんきゅう",
        "back": "研究 \nresearch",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "けんきゅうしゃ",
        "back": "研究者 \nresearcher",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    },
    {
        "front": "けんきゅうしつ",
        "back": "研究室 \nresearch room",
        "chapter": "N4 K18"
    }
]